Finding Aid for Harry Burns Hutchins papers
Bentley Historical Library
- Visual Material
  - Prints (Box 22)
July 11, 1912, July 17, 1912, July 18, 1912, Dec. 17, 1913, Jan. 27, 1914, Feb. 25, 1915, June 25, 1915, March 11, 1919, March 20, 1919
Babst, Earl D., 1870-1967.
Feb. 15, 1898, Dec. 31, 1909, 1910, 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, Jan. 29, 1915, July 28, 1915, July 30, 1915, Aug. 4, 1915, Aug. 23, 1915, Oct. 6, 1915
Barbour, Levi Levis, 1840-1925.
Apr. 8, 1910, Apr. 11, 1910, May 7, 1910, May 20, 1911, Feb. 28, 1912, July 1, 1913, Nov. 20, 1916 June 15, 1917, June 30, 1917, July 9, 1917, Nov. 16, 1917, Jan. 7, 1919, Jan. 16, 1919, Jan. 29, 1919, Feb. 10, 1919, Aug. 15, 1919
Bartelme, Philip George, 1876-1954.
1911, Oct. 29, Nov. 3, 1910 and earlier, Nov. 7, 1910, Sept. 21, 1911, Oct. 30, 1912, Dec. 11, 1912, Feb. 18, 1913, Oct. 2, 1913, Apr. 13, 1914, Nov. 4, 1915, Nov. 8, 1915, Nov. 26, 1915
Bates, Henry Moore, 1869-1949.
1898, 1910, Feb. 1, 1911, Apr. 10, 1911, May 11, 1911, July 6, 1911, Nov. 1, 1912, Dec. 19, 1912, July 11, 1913, Jan. 3, 1914 Jan. 7, 1915, Jan. 21, 1915, Feb. 23, 1915, Feb. 26, 1915, Aug. 7, 1915, Nov. 23, 1915, Nov. 29, 1915, Dec. 9, 1915 Jan. 20, 1916, March 7, 1916, June 5, 1916, Sept. 25, 1916, Nov. 3, 1916, Nov. 28, 1916, Dec. 15, 1916 Jan. 25, 1917, June 19, 1917, Dec. 18, 1917, Jan. 4, 1918, Jan. 7, 1918, Jan. 14, 1918, Jan. 28, 1918, Feb. 12, 1918, March 5, 1918, March 5, 1918, Apr. 5, 1918, May 25, 1918, Nov. 29, 1918 Jan. 7, 1919, Jan. 21, 1919, Jan. 25, 1919, March 12, 1919, March 21, 1919, Oct. 15, 1919, Dec. 22, 1919, May 6, 1920, 1921, 1925, 1929
Beakes, Samuel Willard, 1861-1927
Jan. 1, 1914, March 28, 1916
Beal, Junius E. (Junius Emery), 1860-1942.
Nov. 23, 1909, Nov. 27, 1909, 1910, 1911, 1912, 1913, May 12, 1914, Aug. 3, 1914, Sept. 20, 1914, Jan. 4, 1915 March 1, 1915, Aug. 3, 1915, Sept. 13, 1915, March 2, 1916, March 27, 1916, May 5, 1916, July 13, 1916, Aug. 21, 1917
Bishop, William Warner, 1871-1955
July 8, 1915, July 10, 1917, July 26, 1915, July 28, 1915, Nov. 10, 1915, 1916, March 3, 1917, Oct. 9, 1917 Feb. 4, 1918, Apr. 6, 1918, may 8, 1918, may 18, 1918, Aug. 17, 1916, Sept. 30, 1918, Oct. 8, 1918, Nov. 4, 1918, Nov. 29, 1918 Jan. 4, 1919, Jan. 23, 1919, Feb. 11, 1919, Feb. 21, 1919, May 1, 1919, May 15, 1919, Sept. 25, 1919, Nov. 24, 1919
Boudeman, Dallas
1914, May 27, 1914, [letter suggesting Hutchins become Republican candidate for Governor], May 31, 1916, June 14, 1917, May 7, 1918, Jan. 10, 1919, Apr. 2, 1919, Apr. 28, 1919, June 30, 1919
Bowers, Claude G., 1878-1958.
Dec. 14, 1917
Bryan, William Jennings, 1860-1925
Nov. 16, 1914, Nov. 25, 1914, June 4, 1915, June 7, 1915, June 8, 1915, Jan. 11, 1918
Bulkley, Harry Conant, 1870-1943
1911, 1912, 1913, Mar. 3, 1914, Aug. 5, 1914, Oct. 27, 1914, Nov. 5, 1914, 1915, Jan. 4, 1916, Jan. 8, 1916, Jan. 25, 1916, March 20, 1916, Apr. 7, 1916, May 31, 1916, Dec. 14, 1916 Jan. 6, 1917, Feb. 21, 1917, March 2, 1917, March 6, 1917, May 21, 1917, Nov. 20, 1917, May 6, 1918, May 9, 1918
Burrows, Julius Caesar, 1837-1915
July 14, 1910, March 4, 1911
Burton, Marion LeRoy, 1874-1925
May 8, 1915, Dec. 4, 1919, 1920
Butler, Nicholas Murray, 1862-1947
Oct. 23, 1912, Oct. 26, 1912
Cabot, Hugh, 1872-1945.
Apr. 17, 1929
Chapin, Roy Dikeman, 1880-1936
Aug. 18, 1915, Jan. 22, 1916, Aug. 16, 1918, Jan. 3, 1919, Jan. 8, 1919, Jan. 20, 1919, March 10, 1919
Clements, William Lawrence, 1861-1934.
1910, 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915, 1916, may 16, 1917, July 12, 1917, July 28, 1917, July 31, 1917, Oct. 23, 1917 July 20, 1918, Nov. 13, 1918, March 23, 1919, Oct. 24, 1919, Feb. 4, 1920, Feb. 5, 1920, Feb. 12, 1920, March 5, 1920, Apr. 25, 1920, July 6, 1925, Nov. 10, 1925.
Comstock, William. Alfred, 1877-1949.
May 26, 1913, March 5, 1915, March 13, 1915
Cook, William Wilson, 1858-1930.
June 1, 1910, June 10, 1910, June 13, 1910, Feb. 10, 1911, March 3, 1911, June 1, 1911, June 5, 1911, June 6, 1911 March 6, 1919, Jan. 26, 1920, Feb. 19, 1920, Apr. 12, 1920, May 10, 1920, May 27, 1920, May 28, 1920, June 4, 1920, June 24, 1920, 1921, 1922, 1923, 1924, 1925, Nov. 19, 1928, Dec. 25, 1928, 1929, 1930
Cooley, Charles Horton, 1864-1929.
June 11, 1910, June 13, 1910, Dec. 14, 1909, Dec. 15, 1909, Feb. 27, 1912, Oct. 29, 1912, Apr. 6, 1915
Cooley, Mortimer Elwyn, 1855-1944.
Apr. 18, 1910 and earlier, Dec. 29, 1910, 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915, 1916, 1917, Jan. 8, 1918, Jan. 10, 1918, Jan. 22, 1918, Feb. 25, 1918, May 27, 1918 July 10, 1918, Nov. 16, 1918, May 15, 1919, July 10, 1919, July 12, 1919, Feb. 5, 1920, Feb. 14, 1920, Feb. 20, 1920, Apr. 8, 1925
Copeland, Royal Samuel, 1868-1938
Feb. 19, 1912, Feb. 23, 1912, Feb. 24, 1912, May 8, 1912, Jan. 30, 1913, Feb. 7, 1913
Cramton, Louis Convers, 1875-1966.
Apr., 1916
Daniels, Josephus, 1862-1948.
Apr. 23, 1913, Feb. 5, 1919
Demmon, Isaac Newton, 1842-1920.
May 27, 1910, Nov. 25, 1912
D'Ooge, Martin Luther, 1839-1915
Oct. 17, 1912
Douglas, Lloyd Cassel, 1877-1951.
July 12, 1916, July 19, 1916, Dec. 10, 1916, Dec. 20, 1929
Dow, Earle Wilbur, 1868-1946.
Sept. 14, 1918
DuBois, William Edward Burghardt, 1868-1963
March 30, 1910, Apr. 11, 1910, May 1, 1917, may 8, 1917
Eggert, Carl Edgar, 1868
Oct. 7, 1917, Oct. 11, 1917, Oct. 14, 1917, Oct. 15, 1917, Oct. 16, 1917, Oct. 19, 1917, Oct. 22, 1917, Oct. 24, 1917, Nov. 13, 1917, Nov. 21, 1917
Effinger, John Robert, 1869-1933.
1913, Apr. 18, 1914, Aug. 20, 1914, Aug. 21, 1915
Ferris, Woodbridge Nathan, 1853-1928.
March 11, 1898, Dec. 2, 1912, Dec. 29, 1912, 1913, Feb. 5, 1914, Feb. 11, 1914, March 26, 1914, June 26, 1914, July 2, 1914, Dec. 15, 1914 Jan. 2, 1915, April, 1915, May 10, 1915, Aug. 4, 1915, Aug. 5, 1915, Oct. 17, 1915, Nov. 6, 1915, Feb. 12, 1916, Feb. 16, 1916, Sept. 14, 1918
Fletcher, Frank Ward, 1853-1922.
March 2, 1898, March 3, 1898, Oct. 20, 1898, Nov. 26, 1909, March 3, 1910, June 2, 1910, June 13, 1910, June 16, 1910, June 17, 1910, 1911, Feb. 20, 1912, Feb. 23, 1912, Feb. 26, 1912
Gore, Victor Michael, 1858, 1941.
May 16, 1913, Jan. 20, 1914, Jan. 4, 1915, Jan. 7, 1915, Feb. 13, 1915, March 1, 1915, Apr. 14, 1915, Feb. 28, 1918, Sept. 16, 1918, Nov. 26, 1919, Dec. 3, 1919
Grant, Claudius Buchanan, 1835-1921
Nov. 29, 1897, Dec. 16, 1909, Dec. 20, 1909, June 13, 1910, June 23, 1910, June 30, 1910, July 5, 1910, Dec. 19, 1910, 1911, Jan. 9, 1912, Jan. 11, 1912, May 19, 1912, May 29, 1912, Dec. 22, 1916, Feb. 11, 1919
Grant. John Henry, 1857-1913
Dec. 24, 1909, 1910, 1911, 1912
Groesbeck, Alexander J., 1873-1953.
Nov. 28, 1916
Hanchett, Benjamin Savtell, 1868-1933.
Mar. 25, 1911, June 21, 1911, May 17, 1912, 1912, 1913, May 14, 1914, Apr. 4, 1914, Oct. 23, 1914, 1915, Apr. 20, 1916 Mar. 5, 1917, June 7, 1917, June 14, 1917, July 13, 1917, Sept. 13, 1917, Sept. 15, 1917, Feb. 1, 1918, Feb. 9, 1918, Feb. 14, 1918, Apr. 8, 1918, Apr. 16, 192o
Hart, Albert Bushnell, 1854-1943
Feb. 18, 1898
Hinsdale, Wilbert Bartlett, 1851-1944.
1915-1918
Hobbs, William Herbert, 1864-1953.
Nov. 2, 1910, Feb. 14, 1911, 1912, 1913, Jan. 12, 1914, Feb. 16, 1914, Apr. 1, 1914, Feb. 26, 1915, Mar. 26, 1915, Apr. 21, 1915, Apr. 21, 1915, Nov. 8, 1915, Nov. 15, 1915 Jan. 3, 1917, Mar. 29, 1917, Mar. 30, 1917, Apr. 8, 1917, Dec. 24, 1917, Apr. 25, 1919, May 2, 1919, Jan. 20, 1920
Hoover, Herbert Clark, Pres. U.S., 1874-1964.
Oct. 16, 1914
Hubbard, Lucius Lee, 1849-1933.
1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915, Apr. 8, 1916, Feb. 1918, Apr. 7, 1918, May 27, 1918, Aug. 16, 1918, Oct. 12, 1918, Feb. 10, 1919, Apr. 4, 1919, July 12, 1919, Nov. 10, 1919, Dec. 15, 1919, Feb. 24, 1920
Hudson, Joseph Lovthian, 1846-1912.
Jan. 2, 1912, Jan. 4, 1912, Feb. 21, 1912, Feb. 26, 1912
Hudson, Richard, 1845-1915.
Feb. 14, 1910, May 27, 1910, May 5, 1912, Jan. 26, 1913, Mar. 22, 1913, Oct. 28, 1913, Jan. 23, 1914, Dec. 8, 1914, Jan. 11, 1915, Jan. 18, 1915, Jan. 23, 1915, Feb. 6, 1915
Hughes, Charles Evans, 1862-1948.
Feb. 14, 1907, 1909, Mar. 4, 1914, 1929
Hussey, Ethel Fountain, 1865-1915
Feb. 6, 1913
Hussey, William Joseph, 1862-1926.
Aug. 14, 1912, Dec. 2, 1912, 1913, July 18, 1914, July 21, 1914, Nov. 17, 1914, Aug. 31, 1915, mar. 4, 1917, mar. 15, 1916, May 18, 1916
Illinois Vigilance Association
Sept. 22, 1914
Johnson, Elias Finley, 1861-1933
July 11, 1910, Aug. 9, 1912
Jordan, Myra Beach, 1860
June 9, 1913, July 8, 1913, Nov. 24, 1913, Dec. 4, 1913, Dec. 30, 1913, Jan. 14, 1914, Apr. 21, 1914, June 18, 1914, July 15, 1914, 1914 Jan. 5, 1915, Jan. 18, 1915, Apr. 23, 1915, May 14, 1915, June 28, 1915, Nov. 8, 1915, Dec. 6, 1915, May 19, 1916, June 1, 1916 Oct. 17, 1917, Jan. 10, 1917, Apr. 13, 1918, Aug. 2, 1918, Sept. 22, 1918, Sept. 24, 1918, Oct. 10, 1918, Dec. 7
Keeler, Fred L
Jan. 4, 1915, Jan. 23, 1915, Mar. 12, 1915, Sept. 10, 1915, Feb. 3, 1916, Sept. 20, 1916, Aug. 6, 1917, Oct. 6, 1917, Dec. 21, 1917, Feb. 5, 1918, mar. 18, 1918, Mar. 20, 1918, Mar. 21, 1918, May 15, 1918, Sept. 23, 1918
Kellogg, John Harvey, 1852-1943
Jan. 27, 1916
Kelsey, Francis Willey, 1858-1927
1910, Feb. 1, 1911, July 13, 1911, Feb. 3, 1912, Mar. 2, 1912, Nov. 25, 1912, Nov. 27, 1912, Dec. 21, 1912 Jan. 9, 1913, Jan. 20, 1913, Mar. 14, 1913, May 10, 1913, 1913, 1914, 1915, Feb. 29, 1916, Apr. 22, 1916, Oct. 12, 1916 Jan. 8, 1917, May 21, 1917, July 23, 1917, Jan. 15, 1918, Dec. 10, 1918, Feb. 22, 1919, Feb. 24, 1919, Aug. 1, 1925, Mar. 10, 1926
Knappen, Loyal Edwin, 1854-1930.
1910, 1911
Koch, Theodore Wesley, 1871-1941.
Apr. 12, 1910, Oct. 11, 1910, Oct. 13, 1910, Oct. 22, 1910, Jan. 10, 1911, Feb. 1, 1911, Mar. 29, 1912, Apr. 27, 1912, July 9, 1913, July 15, 1913, Aug. 16, 1913 Mar. 2, 1914, June 15, 1914, Nov. 17, 1914, Apr. 5, 1915, Apr. 15, 1915, Apr. 19, 1915, Dec. 6, 1915
Labadie, Joseph
Oct. 15, 1911, Oct. 27, 1911, Oct. 31, 1911, Nov. 27, 1911, Jan. 2, 1912, Jan. 9, 1912, Feb. 22, 1912, Feb. 27, 1912, Aug. 10, 1912, 1912, June 11, 1913, Nov. 16, 1913, May 12, 1914, June 2, 1914, June 23, 1914, Dec. 29, 1914, Jan. 13, 1920
Lansing, Robert, 1864-1928.
July 1, 1915
League to Enforce Peace.
July 28, 1915, Dec. 6, 1915, Dec. 22, 1915, Nov. 22, 1917 Mar. 23, 1918, Apr. 20, 1918, Apr. 24, 1918, Apr. 27, 1918, Apr. 29, 1918, June 4, 1918, Aug. 13, 1918, Oct. 18, 1918, Nov. 30, 1918, Dec. 31, 1918 Jan. 2, 1919, Jan. 15, 1919, Jan. 29, 1919, Jan. 30, 1919, Apr. 8, 1919, May 4, 1919, June 19, 1919, Sept. 18, 1919, Oct. 7, 1919, Nov. 22, 1919, Nov. 25, 1919, Dec. 5, 1919
Leland, Frank
1910, 1911, 1912, 1913, Dec. 5, 1914, 1915, Feb. 3, 1916, Oct. 18, 1916, Dec. 18, 1916, July 17, 1919
Little, Clarence Cook, 1888
Mar. 2, 1911, Aug. 18, 1911, Aug. 22, 1911, June 29, 1925, Nov. 6, 1925, June 27, 1925, July 2, 1926, June 7, 1927, Apr. 7, 1928
McLaughlin, Andrew Cunningham, 1861-1947.
Oct. 19, 1927
Malcolm, George Arthur, 1881-1961.
Apr. 8, 1913, Mar. 23, 1914
Mapes, Carl Edgar, 1874-1939
June 21, 1917
Mayo, William James, 1861-1939.
Sept. 27, 1915, Sept. 28, 1915
Men's League for Woman Suffrage of the State of Michigan.
Jan. 16, 1912
Mott, John R
Apr. 30, 1912
Murfin, James Orin, 1875-1940
July 23, 1918, Aug. 15, 1918, Aug. 29, 1918, Jan. 29, 1919, Mar. 5, 1919, Mar. 17, 1919, Sept. 4, 1925
National Child Labor Committee.
Jan. 8, 1913, Jan. 12, 1914, Dec. 19, 1914, Dec. 20, 1915, Apr. 22, 1920
National Conference on Race Betterment.
Dec. 24, 1913, Jan. 2, 1914, Mar. 3, 1915
National Conservation Congress.
May 26, 1913, Sept. 20, 1913, Oct. 15, 1913
National Home Finding Society for Colored Children.
Jan. 20, 1920, Apr. 17, 1920
National Peace Federation.
Aug. 20, 1915, Sept. 8, 1915, Oct. 30, 1915
National Religious Training School.
Mar. 12, 1914, Oct. 7, 1914
National Urban League for Social Service Among Negroes.
Apr. 14, 1920
Newberry, Truman Handy, 1864-1945
Nov. 23, 1909, Nov. 27, 1909, Nov. 29, 1909, 1910, 1911, June 19, 1915, May 2, 1918
Osborn, Chase Salmon, 1860-1949.
Nov. 29, 1909 and before, Mar. 12, 1910, Mar. 15, 1910, Apr. 13, 1910, Feb. 16, 1910, 1911, 1912, Oct. 24, 1913, Dec. 6, 1913, Mar. 7, 1914, June 29, 1914, Jan. 15, 1918, June 23, 1920
Page, Walter Hines, 1855-1918.
May 9, 1898
Patrons of Husbandry. Michigan State Grange.
Nov. 15, 1915, Nov. 29, 1915, Dec. 2, 1915
Pillsbury, Walter Bowers, 1872-1960.
Sept. 18, 1912, May 5, 1913
Pinchot, Gifford, 1865-1946.
Oct. 23, 1909, Nov. 2, 1909
Pingree, Hazen Smith, 1840-1901.
Feb. 1, 1898, Apr. 12, 1898, Jan. 21, 1898
Quezon, Manuel Luis, 1878 1944.
Mar. 29, 1912
Reeves, Jesse Siddall, 1872-1942.
mar. 16, 1910, Apr. 12, 1910, Apr. 16, 1910, Apr. 22, 1910
Reighard, Jacob Ellsworth, 1861-1942.
July 15, 1915
Riggs, Henry E.
Aug. 10, 1915, Aug. 20, 1915, Nov. 24, 1916, Dec. 29, 1916, Jan. 23, 1917, Feb. 10, 1917, Mar. 19, 1917, Mar. 26, 1917, Apr. 5, 1917, Nov. 9, 1917 Aug. 28, 1918, Sept. 20, 1918, Nov. 25, 1918, Dec. 16, 1918, Dec. 19, 1918, Mar. 6, 1919, Jan. 1, 1920
Roosevelt, Theodore, Pres. U.S., 1858-1919.
Dec. 2, 1910, Mar. 5, 1917
Root, Elihu
Dec. 29, 1910, Mar. 4, 1914, Oct. 1, 1917, Dec. 17, 1917
Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882
Feb. 14, 1911, Feb. 16, 1911, 1912, June 4, 1913, Oct. 2, 1913, Jan. 13, 1914, June 4, 1914, Aug. 15, 1914, Dec. 1, 1914, June 9, 1915, Feb. 19, 1917, May 11, 1917, Apr. 23, 1918, Apr. 30, 1918
Sawyer, Walter Hulme, 1861-1931.
1909, 1910, 1911, 1912, 1913, 1914, 1915, 1916, Jan. 12, 1917, May 31, 1917, Sept. 29, 1917, Dec. 24, 1918, Nov. 21, 1924, Nov. 30, 1924
Schurman, J.G.
Dec. 16, 1910, Dec. 22, 1910, Dec. 20, 1910, Apr. 5, 1911, Dec. 1, 1911, Dec. 5, 1911, Dec. 7, 1911
Sleeper, Albert E
Mar. 27, 1917, Apr. 11, 1917, Feb. 9, 1918, Apr. 2, 1918, Apr. 3, 1918, Feb. 5, 1919
Smith, Shirley Wheeler
Mar. 20, 1912, Apr. 3, 1912
Smith, William Alden, 1859-1932.
June 6, 1911, Aug. 2, 1911, Feb. 21, 1912, Mar. 29, 1912, Apr. 1, 1912, Apr. 5, 1912, Dec. 20, 1912, July 14, 1913, Feb. 28, 1914
Stimson, Henry Lewis, 1867-1950
May 15, 1912, June 30, 1913
Taft, William Howard, Pres. U.S., 1857-1930.
Apr. 29, 1898, Oct. 22, 1910, Mar. 16, 1912, Oct. 28, 1915
Townsend, Charles E. (Charles Elroy), 1856-1924.
Oct. 20, 1910, Nov. 1, 1910, Dec. 30, 1910, May 3, 1912, Mar. 12, 1913, Mar. 15, 1913, Nov. 29, 1913, Jan. 28, 1916, Jan. 31, 1916, Sept. 7, 1916
Vandenberg, Arthur H.
June 8, 1901, Aug. 911901, June 13, 1902, Jan. 3, 1909, Jan. 18, 1910, Jan. 19, 1910, Jan. 8, 1912
Van Tyne, Claude Halstead, 1869-1930
May 1, 1916, Jan. 3, 1917, Nov. 23, 1911
Vaughan, Victor Clarence, 1851-1929
1910, 1911, 1912, Jan. 4, 1913, May 5, 1913, Sept. 11, 1916, Sept. 10, 1917, Sept. 19, 1917, Oct. 4, 1917, Dec. 19, 1917, Jan. 4, 1918, Jan. 21, 1918, Mar. 6, 1918, Apr. 9, 1918, Dec. 7, 1918
Ward, Marcus Llevellyn, 1875-1963.
Jan. 12, 1916
Warner, Fred Maltby, 1865-1923
Dec. 29, 1909, 1910
Washington, Booker Taliaferro, 1856-1915.
Nov. 30, 1912, Dec. 2, 1912, Dec. 14, 1912, Dec. 21, 1912, Jan. 7, 1913, Jan. 9, 1914, Jan. 14, 1914, Mar. 17, 1914, Oct. 12, 1914, Jan. 6, 1915, May 14, 1915, Oct. 14, 1915, March. 6, 1916
Wedemeyer, William Walter, 1873-1913
Sept. 18, 1911
Wenley, Robert Mark, 1861-1929.
Apr. 9, 1910, Apr. 13, 1910, Mar. 2, 1912, Mar. 30, 1912, Sept. 7, 1912, Sept. 24, 1912, Oct. 21, 1912, Nov. 30, 1912, Apr. 18, 1919, Aug. 6, 1925, 1926, 1927
Wheeler, Burton Kendall, 1882-
Aug. 7, 1901, Mar. 3, 1902, Sept. 2, 1902
White Andrew Dickson, 1832-1918.
June 3, 1898, Dec. 4, 1918
Wilson, Woodrow, Pres. U.S., 1856-1924.
Jan. 15, 1910, Jan. 20, 1910, Jan. 27, 1911, Jan. 15, 1912, Aug. 23, 1912, Jan. 20, 1913, Sept. 2, 1914, June 16, 1915, Nov. 15, 1916
Wood, Leonard, 1860-1927.
June 8, 1914, July 10, 1914, July 14, 1914, Apr. 30, 1915, July 12, 1915, July 16, 1915, Aug. 14, 1915, Mar. 8, 1917, Apr. 18, 1917, Apr. 23, 1917, Jan. 10, 1919
World Court League.
May 2, 1916
World Peace Foundation.
July 10, 1912
Wright, Luther Lamphere, 1856-1922.
1910, 1911, 1912, 1913, Oct. 13, 1914